Hello.
Hello.  Where are you from?
From Nizhny Novgorod.  And you?
I am from Tagil, lower clan, but now I
live in Omsk.  How do you communicate?   I just
dropped by to chat.
What's the situation with gasoline in Nizhny?
What about the oil refinery yesterday?
Yes, I saw it in Kstova.
Well, overall, if there weren't any locations
and people's craziness,
I think it would be fine.  But in
reality, well, there are always traffic jams
everywhere.   I
can get
you 14 liters of 88th grade gasoline.
Eighty-eighth, maybe seventy-
sixth, maybe no,
not 14 liters of eighty-eighth gasoline.
This is ninety-fifth diluted with a thin
ball especially rashny what year
was eighty-eighth.  It
was seventy-sixth and
I remember it as if it were yesterday that it was eighty-second.
And
this is the eighty-eighth.  Ninety-fifth
diluted with dirty urine.
The second was
ninety ninety second was after
eighty second.
Okay, okay.
So what do you think is the cause of all these
problems with gasoline?   What do you
mean because of what?  Don't you know?
Well, I'm interested in your opinion.
Well, firstly,
because of the location of the war.
Due to the deployment of war.  And where is
this war located?
Exlocations.  Eclocations.   Did
you mean escalation?   Yes.  Yes.
So, because of the escalation of the war.  And what
caused the escalation of the war?
Because of the
crazy behavior of people,
when everyone senses that something is coming,
they all run to stock up on Maxim to the
max.  It's the same as it
was with Covid, with buckwheat and
toilet paper, absolutely the same
.
Understood.
So it turns out that people just
rushed around,
they can’t control themselves, they start,
yes, going crazy, they start
drying up
all the energy resources.
That is, there is simply an uncontrolled
purchase of resources.  Everyone wants to buy them.
No, they are trying to stop them.
They are trying to stop it all. No, uncontrolled purchases are
definitely not happening because they are trying to
stop it all.
But not everything works out.  It doesn’t always
work because online payment is
automatic.   Yes.
In any case,
uh, a test purchase only happens
when you come to the checkout.
Then there will be a controlled purchase.
Online payment is still
online payment, and you can
fill up any number of liters at any
gas station.   Yes.
at the terminal, including
self-service.  You
can also add any amount of fuel
.
And I saw, in short, there were fights at
different gas stations.  This is true?   I
don’t know about fights, but perhaps there could
be some, because people
stand for several hours, it happens.
Well, in our city we didn’t have anything like real
fights.  I don't know,
maybe it will appear now,
because yesterday's MPZ,
yes,
one of the central, well, like,
regions, which serves Moscow, and
produces aviation fuel, and,
well, it's the main one, in fact, of the
Ksov region.
Yes, they used to beat up the KSOV there, and yesterday it was
so beautiful in the
beating.  They used to beat her, she burned several
times, but still there
was no such moment.  Anyway, in
any case,
now it turns out that things will be even worse in
Moscow and the Moscow region, yes, because of
this,
yes.  It couldn't get any worse.  It’s as
if it is and will be, but 2 weeks
will pass and everything will be restored.  Well,
yes, but the thing is, look, this doesn’t
mean that nothing will
fly in again.  restore and it
will fly again.   It
will arrive 100%.  Well, who is safe from this
anyway?  No one in Russia is
safe from this.  It's just that,
uh, it's just that, you know, what's your name?
Andrey.
Andrey, my name is Sasha.  Look,
Andrey, what's the point?  The moment is such
that the
entire conflict is being deployed.
escalation,
like an escalator, lift from the word
escalate.
Sorry,
sorry.  Yes, yes, there is a
conflict being localized
in the sense that they are hitting one side.  But you
understand what happened there in Kyiv and
in different regions.
Have you seen it, maybe not?  Recent events,
including what happened.  Well, Russia is
bombing high-rise buildings.  I saw it, it’s not the
first time.
Why multi-story buildings?
Well, in multi-story buildings, yes, residential ones.
Not at all.
Russia is trying to make a location,
you know?  She wants all of this to happen
.
If Russia had tried, it would have
done it long ago.  You you you say, where are
you from?
I am from Omsk.
You spoke from Nizhny Tagil.   I
come from Nizhny Tagil.  I live in
Omsk.
In Omsk or in Tomsk?
Omsk.  These are different cities.  You've had enough of
your Tomsk.
Yes, I know.  I... I'm asking again.  I just did
n't hear.  Omsk right now.
In Omsk.  Yes.  Originally said by Nizhny
Tagil.
I originally said I was from Nizhny
Tagil, but I live in Omsk.
Well, I asked initially, and you
immediately said: "Nizhny Tagil."
No, you said, look, you said, you are from
Nizhny Novgorod.  I say, I’m from
Nizhny Tagil, but now I live in Omsk.
I said so right away.
You didn't say that.
It's just an escalation in your head.
No, not at all.
Well, we didn't say that.
Spoke.
I'm definitely here with this.
Everything is fine.  Come on, let it be for you.   I have
n't said it yet.  Why should I argue about this?
Well, let's agree that you did
n't say that.   That's it
, I didn't say that.
Well, honestly, don't say that.
Yes, I didn't say that.  I've just been in Omsk for
a week now.  I may have forgotten, yes, just to
say this.   Are
you only there for a week?   A
week?  Yes.
What are you doing there?  Are you working?
There you need to look at one object.
Good people asked, they will pay.
Fine.
Where did you go for work?  Well, for
work, yes, I have to.
What do you do?
I am engaged in photography and video shooting.
Ah, damn, that's interesting.   I'm
taking pictures of industrial.
Well, no, no, it's a good profession, normal.
Cool.
It's just that when I was still traveling to Tomsk, a little further
away,
at that time I was still working with dump
equipment, and now I am working with
robotics,
robotic systems.
Aromatization.
Yes, I am currently involved in robotics.
Listen, what do you think, if
Ukraine continues to escalate this, what will
it all lead to?
it will be complete chaos.
I don't even want to think about it, really
.  Honestly,
why do
I find this unpleasant?
It's real, well, it's real, well, it's not
that,
I don't know what to call it, but it's just
real
.  What should we do?
It will just be for everyone.
This is now on the verge of
absolute, in fact.
And it will only get worse.  It will never get better
.
How can the Russians stop all this?
There are options.
How can you turn off the music?  I can't
hear you well because of no
Yes, I can.
What options?   What do you
mean by Russian?  And you are not Russian.
Also Russian too.  Well, how do we like this?  Well,
I am Russian, but I am Jewish by
nationality, but I am Russian.
Well, you've already said a lot, that you're just
, like, the area isn't designated.
I am Jewish.
I am Jewish.  I am not Russian.  Come on, Russian.   Yes.  Yes.
OK.  So good.  Well, sort of
okay.  Well, why do you just
lie then, saying that you are from such and such a
city, and then went there?
By right of the strong, he wanted to take and
deceived.  And what?
For what?  Just for what?  You think I will... But
I'm not Ukrainian.  I won't
insult you.  I will not
blame you for anything.
I tricked you.
I'm not Ukrainian.
I fooled you.
I understand.  I immediately understood to you that I am a
body.  Look, let me show you my
cards.  Look, I'm a Ukrainian from Ukraine, from the
city of Khmelnitsky.  I came here to
insult, humiliate and so on, yes.  But
I decided to pretend to be Russian so that you
would tell me a little about it first, and
now I turn into a real Ukrainian
and say: "I'll send a
Russian."  Oh, see?
Okay, okay.  Well, this way you'll
like everything better.
Well, of course I like it when I get
sent away.  Of course I like it.   I just do
n’t understand why I have to
pretend.
Why just pretend?  You would,
but so as not to scare it away right away, so as not to
scare the fish.   What is there to
scare me about?  There's nothing to be afraid of.
Maybe you're scared?  I don't know.  You
don't have it written all over you: scared, not scared.
I communicate with you adequately.  Like, I'm
not trying to insult you, I'm not trying to.
Understood?  Fine.  Tell me clearly, how are
you, Russians, going to stop this
war?
Personally, I have no plans to do so.
Well, how does Russia plan to get out of this
situation?  Well, Russia will definitely emerge
victorious from this.
How?
Well, how will it work out then?
Look, to win, you need to take
Kyiv, capture it and put it there.
You will dictate the words of Dmitry
Gordon, for example, right?  Like, we
have tactics, we support.   What does
Dmitry Gordon have to do with this?  I don't
understand at all.
Well, no.  And what will you be?  Well, just like that,
well, like you yourself, how do you think Ukraine will
turn out?
Okay, good question.  Look,
Dmitry Gordo is Ukrainian.
No, look, no, not words, but words in words by the
words of Robert Broughdy Madjar,
right?  Because just now in your Kstova
yesterday there was an arrival and the
oil refinery stopped.  And these arrivals are
only getting stronger and stronger with
each passing week.  Yes.  Ukraine has more
and more drones.  And so on.
How many arrivals did Ukraine receive yesterday?
How much
too?  Look, the same as previous
years.  You bombed us and continued to bomb us.
But now, look, but now we have begun to
increase your bombing.  Previously, only
you were shelling us, but now, it
turns out, Ukraine is somehow fighting back.
And quite significantly, because
Ukraine is inflicting such defeats on you that
you are standing in line for gasoline.  You see
, you can’t pour it into canisters either
.  And you fight, you squeal at
gas stations, you fight with each other, because in
order to fill up, you understand?  This is
your inter-Russian spirit, you understand?  So,
yes, things will only get worse and worse for you from now on.
Ukraine will increasingly
increase shelling of Russian
territory.  You will cry and
turn to the
United Nations there.  Be patient.
Can I interrupt you?   I give permission
.
Andrey,
you can.  Thanks a lot.  Andrey, look at the
situation that is happening.  Yes.
And Ukraine is hitting
our regions.  Yes.  Russia responds.
Answers.  In what brief?
No, no, no, it is not Ukraine that is attacking, but Russia that
is responding.  This is what they are answering you.  It was you who attacked
us and you are receiving a
response.  Don't confuse your minds with the idea that
Ukraine is attacking and you are responding.  Yes, you
climbed on us, you beat us, and you
get a response.
Firstly, I didn’t insult you, and
secondly,
I am insulting you.  So what,
Russian?  Do you understand?  Smely prieda.
Look at what you've come for.  If you can't
do something, then sit and keep quiet, you understand?
So, what about you?
And what?  [laughter] You can
barely breathe
now.  I would, I would, I would, look, you're
just so brave because you're
sitting there, you know?  That's all.  Well,
I talk about likes absolutely calmly.   That's
all, you understand?  Now your breathing
quickened.  Okay, let's go.
That's how I love you.  Russia responds.
No, we are answering you.  It is you who are
responsible.  Like, subscribe, comment.
Subscribe to our Telegram right away.  Ось
він.  And the priest.
It's even more and more important.  YouTube is banning
us through karger.  And too
many videos are not shown to people regularly, and
information about the stream is not shown.
Therefore, in order for us to quickly
sign up immediately.  And the message
there in the telegram is also useful and
valuable information, and we are obliged to work with you to ensure
consistent operational communication.   It
doesn’t matter if YouTube shows you about
it.  Glory to Ukraine!